<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Glostars</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_feed">MainFeed</string>
    <string-array name="genders">
        <item name="Male">Male</item>
        <item name="Female">Female</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="iam">
        <item name="User">User</item>
        <item name="Investor">Investor</item>
        <item name="Sponsor/Advertiser">Sponsor/Advertiser</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="occupation">
        <item>Occupation</item>
        <item>Student</item>
        <item>Businessman</item>
        <item>Photographer</item>
        <item>Unemployed</item>
        <item>Service Holder</item>
        <item>Doctor</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_user_profile">user_profile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_test">test</string>
    <string name="light">
        Applying the light in a right way will make good impression by any photo you take – that is why it is an essential thing to keep in mind. You can get the best shot when the subject is lit from the side or from the front.
    </string>

    <string name="zoom">
        If you want to take a good picture, forget about zooming using your phone! A better solution for zooming is to move yourself or change an angle you want to take picture from. If moving is not possible, you can crop the picture later to get the desired shot.
    </string>

    <string name="backgroundtips">
        I can\'t even describe how often I\'ve taken a great shot, only to be unable to enter it into a contest because something in the background doesn\'t look right. So before you click that button, make sure that everything looks right. Learning how to see the world like your camera does can help with this.
    </string>
    <string name="frame">
        Try to place the objects in the foreground to frame the main subjects in your picture. Windows, arches, doorways etc. can form natural frames. 
    </string>

    <string name="perspective">
        Pictures taken from different angles are more buzzworthy. Change your place and take some original shots! Try to use apps as well to add some special effects. 
    </string>

    <string name="crop">
        Nowadays we all have hectic lifestyles so very often we don’t have much time to think carefully about the composition when taking a picture, so the advice is to take a wider picture. You can modify it latter by cropping unnecessary parts if needed.  </string>
    <string name="apps">
        There are a lot of apps on the market that can add significant value to the picture and allow to use DLSR camera functions and special effects while shooting. Don’t be afraid to get the best shot possible. </string>
    <string name="phnfeatures">
        Don’t forget that your phone camera has a set of features itself without using extra apps. For example, you can use HDR or turn on the grid which will help you to shoot according to the rule of thirds. As well, you can set the exposure and choose the amount of light in the picture.
    </string>

    <string name="Terms">
        •	To win prizes a user must complete his or her profile (i.e. Upload Profile Picture and fill in other requested information). Any picture submitted to win prizes will not be considered if the user has not provided the requested information to complete his or her profile.
\n\n•	Amount of pictures that can be submitted in the competition is not limited but it should be within the limit of total number of pictures a user can have in his or her profile.
\n\n•	Only one rating by a registered user will be considered, however a user can change the rating at any time.
\n\n•	Photos with identifiable watermarks (any text or date embedded in the image) will not be considered for the competition.
\n\n•	Any picture submitted by an international celebrity or a picture of an international celebrity will not be considered for winning the prizes.
\n\n•	Users will be responsible for any dispute related to the originality and ownership of the picture.
\n\n•	Glostars rewarding mechanism aims to promote individuals’ photography skill; therefore, any downloaded picture will not be considered for winning prizes in competition.
\n\n•	While uploading any picture please use your common sense.
\n\n•	If any user misuses the platform to win the competition, then all the pictures of that user will be disqualified from the competition for that term.
\n\n•	Submission of pictures for Jan – Apr 2017 competition term ends on April 30th at midnight (23:59) Eastern European Time. Rating period also ends on April 30th at midnight (23:59) Eastern European Time.
\n\n•	There will be one picture of the week prize starting from January 1 until April 23, 2017. First picture of the week will be selected among all the pictures submitted from January 1 – 22, 2017
\n\n•	All prizes must be claimed within one (1) week after announcement. It is preferred to collect it personally then other alternatives must be agreed with Glostars.
\n\n•	If sending the prize is not possible to the location of the winner, then Glostars reserves all the rights to take alternative decision.
\n\n•	The distribution of prize may take up to two (2) months depending on the location of the winner.
\n\n•	One user can win only one (1) of the grand prizes (If one user wins more than one position for the final prizes then only the highest one will be considered), also (1) one of the picture of the week prizes and (1) one of the monthly prizes.
\n\n•	Pictures submitted in the Hashtag (#) competition by Glostars are eligible for Hashtag (#) competition prizes and Grand Prizes only.
\n\n•	Same picture which won week competition will not be considered for the monthly prize, but other picture of the same user can be considered if uploaded in that particular month.
\n\n•	In order to claim any prize, you will have to proof your identity by providing valid document.
\n\n•	Glostars may use the winning picture for marketing purpose with permission of the owner.
\n\n•	Individual picture of the winner must be sent to Glostars while claiming the prize, which will be used for marketing purpose.
\n\n•	Glostars current employees, sponsors of the prizes, investors and other individuals directly related with Glostars cannot win any of the prizes.
\n\n•	Overall, Glostars reserves all the rights to disqualify any picture which the company considers to be inappropriate.


    </string>

    <string name="mainterms">

        1. You have to be minimum 13 years old to use the service.

\n\n2. You may not post violent, nude, partially nude, discriminatory, unlawful, infringing, hateful, pornographic or sexually suggestive photos or other similar content via the Service.

\n\n3. While uploading any picture please use your common sense

\n\n4. You are responsible for any activity that occurs through your account and you agree you will not sell, transfer, license or assign your account, followers, username, or any account rights. You also agree that all information you provide or provided to Glostars upon registration and at all other times is true, accurate, current and complete and you agree to update your information as necessary to maintain its truth and accuracy.

\n\n5. You agree that you will not ask, collect or use the login credentials of other Glostars users.

\n\n6. You are responsible for keeping your log in credentials secret and secure.

\n\n7. You must not defame, stalk, bully, abuse, harass, threaten, impersonate or intimidate people or entities and you must not post private or confidential information via the Service, including, without limitation, your or any other person\'s credit card information, social security or alternate national identity numbers, non-public phone numbers or non-public email addresses.

\n\n8. You may not use the Service for any illegal or unauthorized purpose. You agree to comply with all laws, rules and regulations (for example, federal, state, local and provincial) applicable to your use of the Service and your Content (defined below), including but not limited to, copyright laws.

\n\n9. You are solely responsible for your conduct and any data, text, files, information, usernames, images, graphics, photos, profiles, audio and video clips, sounds, musical works, works of authorship, applications, links and other content or materials (collectively, "Content") that you submit, post or display on or via the Service.

\n\n10. You must not change, modify, adapt or alter the Service or change, modify or alter another website so as to falsely imply that it is associated with the Service or Glostars.

\n\n11. You must not create or submit unwanted email, comments, stars or other forms of commercial or harassing communications (a/k/a "spam") to any Glostars users.

\n\n12. You must not use domain names or web URLs in your username without prior written consent from Glostars.

\n\n13. You must not interfere or disrupt the Service or servers or networks connected to the Service, including by transmitting any worms, viruses, spyware, malware or any other code of a destructive or disruptive nature. You may not inject content or code or otherwise alter or interfere with the way any Glostars page is rendered or displayed in a user\'s browser or device.

\n\n14. You must not create accounts with the Service through unauthorized means, including but not limited to, by using an automated device, script, bot, spider, crawler or scraper.

\n\n15. You must not attempt to restrict another user from using or enjoying the Service and you must not encourage or facilitate violations of these Terms of Use or any other Glostars terms.

\n\n16. Violation of these Terms of Use may, in Glostars\'s sole discretion, result in termination of your Glostars account. You understand and agree that Glostars cannot and will not be responsible for the Content posted on the Service and you use the Service at your own risk. If you violate the letter or spirit of these Terms of Use, or otherwise create risk or possible legal exposure for Glostars, we can stop providing all or part of the Service to you.

\n\n17. Glostars may use the content for marketing purpose with the consent of owner.

\n\n\n\nService : Here the term service has been defined as the Glostars website offering facility to upload, host, share, star, report and delete picture; also the opportunity to compete for prizes based on the stars provided by the registered users.
    </string>

    <string name="aboutus">
        Glostars is a photo-sharing platform which allows individuals, groups or organizations to share pictures among global audience. In contrast to existing platforms, it has competition feature running on regular basis where a user can win exciting prizes based on community voting. Moreover, Glostars is not only a platform for competing for prizes, user can share picture among very limited circle or for all too; thus user has full freedom in sharing picture here at Glostars. Additionally, we do not take the rights of the content shared on our platform. Thus you can share your content without fear of losing the rights on it!

    </string>

    <string name="offers">
        Currently user can share, star (or vote) picture and grow network among a global community. While sharing picture, a user can share it only among mutual followers (i.e. when both parties are following each other) or with public or can submit in photo competition. Among the pictures submitted in competition, we give prizes to the highest starred (or voted) picture every week, every month and finally the grand prizes at the end of competition term (i.e. after every 4 months in a calendar year). Moreover, at the end of the competition term we organize Photo Exhibition with top 50 pictures of that term.
    </string>


    <string name="difference">
        •	We reward and recognize people’s photography on regular basis through prizes and spot in exhibition
        \n•	We do not take copyrights of the shared picture
        \n•	We offer better control in sharing your pictures online

    </string>

    <string name="achievements">
        We started our operation globally in January 2016. And in this short time we have awarded more than 80 pictures coming from different parts of the world. Also, we have organized 3 international photo exhibitions in Finland portraying over 150 top voted pictures.
    </string>

    <string name="what">
        Glostars is a photo-sharing platform where you can upload pictures to share with friends or public or to submit in photo competition. Along with connecting you with your friends we aim to reward and recognize the pictures you share on our platform based on community voting.
    </string>

    <string name="who">Starting from 13 years old anyone can Sign up at Glostars. </string>

    <string name="cost">No, the service is completely free of charge. </string>

    <string name="copyright">No, Glostars does not reserve the rights on the shared pictures unlike many other photo sharing services. </string>

    <string name="prizes">Anyone who submit pictures in competition in accordance to terms and conditions can win prizes. </string>

    <string name="winners">Winners are selected based on the highest number of stars (or rating). </string>

    <string name="seepics">You can either make a picture visible for public or only for your friends. </string>

    <string name="comptheme">No, you can submit any photo complying with terms and conditions of the competition. </string>
    <string name="cameragood">No, the quality of the photo is not the focus point, matter is the popularity of your picture. </string>
    <string name="security">All the information and contents uploaded at Glostars are hosted at Microsoft platform, which ensures highest possible security. </string>
    <string name="collectprize">All prizes must be claimed within one week after announcement. It is preferred to collect it in person but other alternatives must be agreed with Glostars. </string>
    <string name="dataprivacy">Data file description in accordance with Section 10 of the Personal Data Act (523/1999)
1. Data Controller
\nBusiness-ID: 2709046-4
\nAddress: Punkkerikatu 5 A 17
\nDomicile: Lappeenranta, Finland
\nTel. +358 466 415 379
\nE-mail: mustafa.corporaterra@gmail.com
\n\nPerson in charge of matters relating to the personal data file and contact person:
\nNawrin Binte Nawab
\nE-mail: nawrinrani@gmail.com
\n\n2. Name of the Personal Data File
\nglostars-data
\n\n3. Purpose for the Handling of Personal Data
\nPersonal Data contained in the Personal Data File is handled solely for the purposes of developing and improving the Service, communicating with users, optimization of advertisements, ensuring safety and security.

4. Recorded Data
\nThe following data will be recorded in the personal data file:
\nNames
\nLocation (city and country)
\nSelectedLanguage of use
\nDate of birth
\nGender
\nPhone numbers
\nE-mail addresses
\n\nAny other information required for providing the services
\n\n5. Regular Sources of Data
\nThe data to be recorded in the personal data file is regularly acquired in the following manners:

\n\nThe data provided by the users in connection with entering into the customer agreement of Service Usage.
\nAdditional Data may be acquired directly from users by e-mail, telephone or other appropriate mean.
\n\n6. Disclosure and Transfer of Personal
\nData recorded in the personal data file may be disclosed within and outside of EU only in the following situations:

\n\nGlostars Oy may disclose data in the customer and user register within the limits set by applicable legal provisions and the terms of use of the Service.

\nPersonal data may be disclosed, for example, to partners related to customer benefits.
\nUnless required by law, personal data is not regularly disclosed to third parties except for the purposes specified above.
\n\n7. Security of the Register
\nThe IT network and equipment where the data file is stored are located behind a firewall and are protected with other technical means as well. Only specified authorized persons have access to the data. These persons have signed valid confidentiality agreements.

\n\n8. Right of Access and Correction of Data
In compliance with Section 26 of the Personal Data Act, everyone is entitled to access the data regarding him/her that has been registered onto the personal data file. A signed right of access request should be submitted in writing to:
\n\n9 Cookies
\nWe use HTTP cookies on our website. A cookie is a small text file sent to and stored on the user’s computer. It allows the website operator to identify regular visitors, enables easier logging in to services and facilitates the collection of consolidated data regarding visitors. This information helps us to continuously develop our website content and functionality. Cookies are not harmful to the computer or files of the users. We use cookies to provide personalized information and better service to our customers. We also collect data on users logged into the service for the purpose of session management. For example, collecting log data allows us to more effectively assist customers in problem situations.


\n\n\nGlostars Oy
\n53850 Lappeenranta, Finland
\nPunkkerikatu 5 A 17
\nOn your right of access request, please mention that the request concerns data in Glostars customer register.
</string>

    <string name="title_activity_notifications">notifications</string>
    <string name="title_activity_notification">Notification</string>
    <string name="title_activity_upload">upload</string>
    <string name="title_activity_competition_all">competitionAll</string>
    <string name="title_activity_edit_profile">edit_profile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_competition_user">competitionUser</string>
    <string name="title_activity_editprofile">Editprofile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_competition_feed">competitionFeed</string>

    <string name="title_activity_image_full_screen">imageFullScreen</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_comment_model">commentModel</string>
    <string name="title_activity_search_results">searchResults</string>
    <string name="title_activity_competition_page">competition_page</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_competition_gallery">competitionGallery</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tips">tips</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings_page">settingsPage</string>
    <string name="title_activity_followers_page">followersPage</string>
    <string name="title_activity_terms_main">TermsMain</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fragment_image_slider">fragmentImageSlider</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_us">AboutUs</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_new_feed">newFeed</string>
    <string name="signupemail">A confirmation mail has been sent to your email address. Please check your email to successfully open an account</string>
</resources>
