<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Glostars</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_feed">MainFeed</string>
    <string-array name="genders">
        <item name="Gender">Gender</item>
        <item name="Male">Male</item>
        <item name="Female">Female</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="occupation">
        <item>Occupation</item>
        <item>Student</item>
        <item>Businessman</item>
        <item>Photographer</item>
        <item>Unemployed</item>
        <item>Service Holder</item>
        <item>Doctor</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="title_activity_user_profile">user_profile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_test">test</string>
    <string name="light">
        Applying the light in a right way will make good impression by any photo you take – that is why it is an essential thing to keep in mind. You can get the best shot when the subject is lit from the side or from the front.
    </string>

    <string name="zoom">
        If you want to take a good picture, forget about zooming using your phone! A better solution for zooming is to move yourself or change an angle you want to take picture from. If moving is not possible, you can crop the picture later to get the desired shot.
    </string>

    <string name="backgroundtips">
        I can\'t even describe how often I\'ve taken a great shot, only to be unable to enter it into a contest because something in the background doesn\'t look right. So before you click that button, make sure that everything looks right. Learning how to see the world like your camera does can help with this.
    </string>
    <string name="frame">
        Try to place the objects in the foreground to frame the main subjects in your picture. Windows, arches, doorways etc. can form natural frames. 
    </string>

    <string name="perspective">
        Pictures taken from different angles are more buzzworthy. Change your place and take some original shots! Try to use apps as well to add some special effects. 
    </string>

    <string name="crop">
        Nowadays we all have hectic lifestyles so very often we don’t have much time to think carefully about the composition when taking a picture, so the advice is to take a wider picture. You can modify it latter by cropping unnecessary parts if needed.  </string>
    <string name="apps">
        There are a lot of apps on the market that can add significant value to the picture and allow to use DLSR camera functions and special effects while shooting. Don’t be afraid to get the best shot possible. </string>
    <string name="phnfeatures">
        Don’t forget that your phone camera has a set of features itself without using extra apps. For example, you can use HDR or turn on the grid which will help you to shoot according to the rule of thirds. As well, you can set the exposure and choose the amount of light in the picture.
    </string>

    <string name="Terms">
        •	To win prizes a user must complete his or her profile (i.e. Upload Profile Picture and fill in other requested information). Any picture submitted to win prizes will not be considered if the user has not provided the requested information to complete his or her profile.
\n\n•	Amount of pictures that can be submitted in the competition is not limited but it should be within the limit of total number of pictures a user can have in his or her profile.
\n\n•	Only one rating by a registered user will be considered, however a user can change the rating at any time.
\n\n•	Photos with identifiable watermarks (any text or date embedded in the image) will not be considered for the competition.
\n\n•	Any picture submitted by an international celebrity or a picture of an international celebrity will not be considered for winning the prizes.
\n\n•	Users will be responsible for any dispute related to the originality and ownership of the picture.
\n\n•	Glostars rewarding mechanism aims to promote individuals’ photography skill; therefore, any downloaded picture will not be considered for winning prizes in competition.
\n\n•	While uploading any picture please use your common sense.
\n\n•	If any user misuses the platform to win the competition, then all the pictures of that user will be disqualified from the competition for that term.
\n\n•	Submission of pictures for Jan – Apr 2017 competition term ends on April 30th at midnight (23:59) Eastern European Time. Rating period also ends on April 30th at midnight (23:59) Eastern European Time.
\n\n•	There will be one picture of the week prize starting from January 1 until April 23, 2017. First picture of the week will be selected among all the pictures submitted from January 1 – 22, 2017
\n\n•	All prizes must be claimed within one (1) week after announcement. It is preferred to collect it personally then other alternatives must be agreed with Glostars.
\n\n•	If sending the prize is not possible to the location of the winner, then Glostars reserves all the rights to take alternative decision.
\n\n•	The distribution of prize may take up to two (2) months depending on the location of the winner.
\n\n•	One user can win only one (1) of the grand prizes (If one user wins more than one position for the final prizes then only the highest one will be considered), also (1) one of the picture of the week prizes and (1) one of the monthly prizes.
\n\n•	Pictures submitted in the Hashtag (#) competition by Glostars are eligible for Hashtag (#) competition prizes and Grand Prizes only.
\n\n•	Same picture which won week competition will not be considered for the monthly prize, but other picture of the same user can be considered if uploaded in that particular month.
\n\n•	In order to claim any prize, you will have to proof your identity by providing valid document.
\n\n•	Glostars may use the winning picture for marketing purpose with permission of the owner.
\n\n•	Individual picture of the winner must be sent to Glostars while claiming the prize, which will be used for marketing purpose.
\n\n•	Glostars current employees, sponsors of the prizes, investors and other individuals directly related with Glostars cannot win any of the prizes.
\n\n•	Overall, Glostars reserves all the rights to disqualify any picture which the company considers to be inappropriate.


    </string>

    <string name="mainterms">

        1. You have to be minimum 13 years old to use the service.

\n\n2. You may not post violent, nude, partially nude, discriminatory, unlawful, infringing, hateful, pornographic or sexually suggestive photos or other similar content via the Service.

\n\n3. While uploading any picture please use your common sense

\n\n4. You are responsible for any activity that occurs through your account and you agree you will not sell, transfer, license or assign your account, followers, username, or any account rights. You also agree that all information you provide or provided to Glostars upon registration and at all other times is true, accurate, current and complete and you agree to update your information as necessary to maintain its truth and accuracy.

\n\n5. You agree that you will not ask, collect or use the login credentials of other Glostars users.

\n\n6. You are responsible for keeping your log in credentials secret and secure.

\n\n7. You must not defame, stalk, bully, abuse, harass, threaten, impersonate or intimidate people or entities and you must not post private or confidential information via the Service, including, without limitation, your or any other person\'s credit card information, social security or alternate national identity numbers, non-public phone numbers or non-public email addresses.

\n\n8. You may not use the Service for any illegal or unauthorized purpose. You agree to comply with all laws, rules and regulations (for example, federal, state, local and provincial) applicable to your use of the Service and your Content (defined below), including but not limited to, copyright laws.

\n\n9. You are solely responsible for your conduct and any data, text, files, information, usernames, images, graphics, photos, profiles, audio and video clips, sounds, musical works, works of authorship, applications, links and other content or materials (collectively, "Content") that you submit, post or display on or via the Service.

\n\n10. You must not change, modify, adapt or alter the Service or change, modify or alter another website so as to falsely imply that it is associated with the Service or Glostars.

\n\n11. You must not create or submit unwanted email, comments, stars or other forms of commercial or harassing communications (a/k/a "spam") to any Glostars users.

\n\n12. You must not use domain names or web URLs in your username without prior written consent from Glostars.

\n\n13. You must not interfere or disrupt the Service or servers or networks connected to the Service, including by transmitting any worms, viruses, spyware, malware or any other code of a destructive or disruptive nature. You may not inject content or code or otherwise alter or interfere with the way any Glostars page is rendered or displayed in a user\'s browser or device.

\n\n14. You must not create accounts with the Service through unauthorized means, including but not limited to, by using an automated device, script, bot, spider, crawler or scraper.

\n\n15. You must not attempt to restrict another user from using or enjoying the Service and you must not encourage or facilitate violations of these Terms of Use or any other Glostars terms.

\n\n16. Violation of these Terms of Use may, in Glostars\'s sole discretion, result in termination of your Glostars account. You understand and agree that Glostars cannot and will not be responsible for the Content posted on the Service and you use the Service at your own risk. If you violate the letter or spirit of these Terms of Use, or otherwise create risk or possible legal exposure for Glostars, we can stop providing all or part of the Service to you.

\n\n17. Glostars may use the content for marketing purpose with the consent of owner.

\n\n\n\nService : Here the term service has been defined as the Glostars website offering facility to upload, host, share, star, report and delete picture; also the opportunity to compete for prizes based on the stars provided by the registered users.
    </string>

    <string name="title_activity_notifications">notifications</string>
    <string name="title_activity_notification">Notification</string>
    <string name="title_activity_upload">upload</string>
    <string name="title_activity_competition_all">competitionAll</string>
    <string name="title_activity_edit_profile">edit_profile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_competition_user">competitionUser</string>
    <string name="title_activity_editprofile">Editprofile</string>

    <string name="title_activity_image_full_screen">imageFullScreen</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_comment_model">commentModel</string>
    <string name="title_activity_search_results">searchResults</string>
    <string name="title_activity_competition_page">competition_page</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_competition_gallery">competitionGallery</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tips">tips</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings_page">settingsPage</string>
    <string name="title_activity_followers_page">followersPage</string>
</resources>
